AUDREY BORGRA

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CONTACT

217.691.7494 AUDREY.BORGRA@GMAIL.COM GITHUB.COM/ABORGRA LINKEDIN.COM/IN/AUDREYBORGRA/

SKILLS

- JAVASCRIPT
- REACT
- HTML
- GIT/GITHUB
- CSS
- BOOTSTRAP
- AGILE

PROJECTS

FEED FIDO - FRONT-END CAPSTONE

- Accountability for pet care chores can be a challenge for both parents and children. I created an app that allows parents to assign daily and recurring pet care chores to their children and easily track completed chores on a daily and weekly basis. Children are able to see a simple dashboard with only their assigned chores for the day.
- This single-page app has full CRUD functionality and was created utilizing React, React Router, and API fetch calls to JSON server. Styling was achieved through CSS, Bootstrap, and Reactstrap to create a simple, user-friendly experience. ChartJS was utilized to create child-specific graphs for completed chores. MomentJS was used to create recurring chores and to easily filter chores based on the day.

HOLIDAY ROAD

- Created an itinerary builder application as a group with a focus on a specific client persona
- Individually responsible for the Javascript functionality involved in the building of the API calls, user choice selections and saving, sorting and filtering functionalities, and displaying of results to the DOM
- Took lead on Javascript functionality and coordinated with group utilizing source control for smooth integration of individual components

EDUCATION

NASHVILLE SOFTWARE SCHOOL
CERTIFICATE, SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT
UNIVERSITY OF PHOENIX

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, HEALTH ADMINISTRATION

JOHN A LOGAN COLLEGE

ASSOCIATES, DIAGNOSTIC MEDICAL SONOGRAPHY

ABOUT ME

Prior to beginning my journey in software development, I worked for over 12 years as an Echo/vascular technologist in the healthcare field. I enjoyed the opportunity that healthcare gave me to help others and make a difference in peoples' lives. It allowed me to solve complex problems using logic while working in a team environment. When a family member introduced me to software development, I realized that the tech field would allow me to continue to use those skills I enjoyed, while not being so physically wearing on my body. This started my love of software that has continued to grow with every new technology I encounter.

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

NASHVILLE SOFTWARE SCHOOL | NOV 2019 - MAY 2020

Intensive full-time 6 month software development program learning full-stack technologies through the creation of applications individually and in the group setting.

- Git and GitHub for version control
- Simulated agile work environment
- Created one page applications using diverse tech stacks including HTML5, CSS3, javaScript, and React.js, and Bootstrap

LEAD ECHO TECHNOLOGIST

ASCENSION ST THOMAS MIDTOWN | AUG 2018 - PRESENT

- Led a team of 10 Echo Technologists in multi-site inpatient and outpatient labs
- Responsible for daily operations of the lab including staff scheduling, patient care, and problem solving
- Trained new staff members
- Quality assurance of technical staff to ensure accuracy of clinical skills and continuing education
- Examination protocol development and implementation- Led multi-modality lab accreditation
- Active involvement in Imaging Council which oversaw cardiac testing policies throughout all Middle Tennessee campuses
- Coordinated with physicians to ensure quality and accuracy in test results

LEAD ECHO TECHNOLOGIST

ADVOCATE MEDICAL GROUP | SEPT 2010 - JULY 2018

- Technical Director/Lead Echovascular Technologist responsible for program development and management of multiple labs
- EMR Super-user charged with training staff members with new EMR system implementation
- Training of new clinical and nonclinical staff members
- Protocol and procedure development for testing, patient scheduling, patient care, and billing
- Oversaw staff scheduling, patient registration, and billing- Led quality assurance on testing and procedures
- Responsible for the initiation of a stand alone vein clinic including overall
 office procedures and protocols, scheduling templates, billing, reporting
 standards, equipment purchasing, and marketing
- Performed diagnostic imaging and acted as an assistant to the physician during all vein procedures
- Worked closely with physicians and technologists to develop best practices for the lab
- Continuously updated practices to remain current with new standards of care

ECHO TECHNOLOGIST

HSHS ST. JOHNS & ST. ANTHONYS | SEPT 2007 - SEPT 2010

- Responsible for the performance of adult and pediatric transthoracic echocardiograms, fetal echocardiograms, stress echocardiograms, transesophageal echocardiograms, and intracardiac echocardiograms
- Worked with a team to ensure excellent patient care
- Role included mentorship and teaching of echocardiography students
- Assisted with quality assurance and continuing education